{
"question": "頭-1",
"answer": "あたま"
},
{
"question": "日曜日",
"answer": "にちようび"
},
{
"question": "誕生日",
"answer": "たんじょうび"
},
{
"question": "可愛い",
"answer": "かわいい"
},
{
"question": "鞄",
"answer": "かばん"
},
{
"question": "土曜日",
"answer": "どようび"
},
{
"question": "月曜日",
"answer": "げつようび"
},
{
"question": "金曜日",
"answer": "きんようび"
},
{
"question": "花瓶",
"answer": "かびん"
},
{
"question": "木曜日",
"answer": "もくようび"
},
{
"question": "本棚",
"answer": "ほんだな"
},
{
"question": "石鹸",
"answer": "せっけん"
},
{
"question": "水曜日",
"answer": "すいようび"
},
{
"question": "飴",
"answer": "あめ"
},
{
"question": "八百屋",
"answer": "やおや"
},
{
"question": "成る",
"answer": "なる"
},
{
"question": "より",
"answer": "より"
},
{
"question": "一番",
"answer": "いちばん"
},
{
"question": "私",
"answer": "わたし"
},
{
"question": "外",
"answer": "そと"
},
